It’s good to enjoy food, but sometimes stories about the dangers of eating certain things can be hard to digest.
享受美食感觉很好，但有时候关于某些食物存在危害的说法却让人难以接受。
I love to tuck into a pepperoni pizza or munch on a jam doughnut, even though I know the dangers that lurk in their ingredients.
我喜欢大快朵颐意大利辣香肠披萨，或者津津有味地咀嚼果酱甜甜圈，尽管我知道它们的配料中潜藏着健康风险。
It’s clear that processed foods are not the most nutritious things; but there now comes a new threat - from ultra-processed foods.
显然，加工食品并非最有营养的食物，但如今又出现了一种新的威胁——来自超加工食品。
Scientists have now discovered that eating these types of food - such as chicken nuggets, ice cream and breakfast cereals - have been linked to early death and poor health.
科学家们现已发现，食用这类食物——比如鸡块、冰淇淋和早餐麦片——会导致早逝和健康状况不佳。
This is the stuff that has been through more substantial industrial processing and often has long ingredient lists on the packet, including added preservatives, sweeteners or colour enhancers.
这类食物经过了更为复杂的工业加工，包装上的配料表通常很长，包含添加防腐剂、甜味剂或色素增强剂等成分。
Knowing that your bowl of cornflakes could be bad for you might be hard to swallow, but two studies have shown that people eating more ultra-processed food had worse heart health.
得知自己吃的一碗玉米片可能对健康有害，或许会让人难以接受，但两项研究均表明，食用超加工食品较多的人，心脏健康状况更差。
Dr Mathilde Touvier from the University of Paris, who conducted one of the studies, told the BBC: "The rapid and worldwide increasing consumption of ultra-processed foods, to the detriment of less processed foods, may drive a substantial burden of cardiovascular diseases in the next decades."
巴黎大学的玛蒂尔德·图维耶博士主持了其中一项研究，她向英国广播公司表示：“在全球范围内，超加工食品的消费量正快速增长，而低加工食品的消费却在减少，这可能会在未来几十年给心血管疾病带来沉重负担。”
But it might not be completely necessary to change your diet just yet as there is still some uncertainty about the results of the study and questions still to answer.
不过，目前或许还没有必要彻底改变饮食习惯，因为研究结果仍存在一些不确定性，还有不少问题有待解答。
Kevin McConway, a professor of statistics at The Open University, told the BBC: "These studies do increase my confidence that there's something real behind these associations - but I'm still far from sure."
开放大学的统计学教授凯文·麦康威向英国广播公司表示：“这些研究确实让我更相信，这些关联背后存在真实的影响——但我还远不能完全确定。”
Maybe we should follow the advice of The US National Institutes of Health, which found that ultra-processed foods lead people to eat more and put on more weight.
或许我们应该听从美国国立卫生研究院的建议，该机构发现，超加工食品会让人吃得更多、越来越胖。
It suggests avoiding food containing ingredients you cannot pronounce or anything your grandmother would not recognise as food!
建议避免食用含有你无法发音的配料的食物，或者你祖母认不出是食物的东西！
The obvious thing to do seems to be to feast on more unprocessed foods, such as fruit, vegetables, fish, nuts and seeds, beans, lentils and wholegrains, often called a Mediterranean-style diet.
最明显的做法似乎是多享用未加工食品，比如水果、蔬菜、鱼类、坚果和籽类、豆类、小扁豆和全谷物——这类饮食通常被称为地中海式饮食。
After all, we are what we eat!
毕竟，我们吃什么，就是什么！